<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Notes...</title>
    <link>https://danward79.github.io/categories/misc/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Notes...</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://danward79.github.io/categories/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://danward79.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 19:42:33 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danward79.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you have landed here, I wonder how you found your way..&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;how&#34;&gt;How&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These pages are hosted as a static site on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.github.com&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;, the static content which forms the pages, is generated with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.golang.org&#34;&gt;Go&lt;/a&gt; tool called &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what&#34;&gt;What&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On these pages you&amp;rsquo;ll find some short posts about things/projects/info, which I have taken notes to remember. These pages are for me to recall, how I have done a task and are as such my &amp;ldquo;Note Book&amp;rdquo;. I happen to share them, as I hope someone else may find them useful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may also from time to time see &amp;ldquo;other&amp;rdquo; posts. Which will be of anything I choose. Such as flashes of past work or anything else I choose to publish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where possible, I do try to give credit by references if they where useful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;why&#34;&gt;Why&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mainly just for my recollection and sometimes, I like to write some stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;when&#34;&gt;When&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are no schedules. I make no promises..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;C&amp;rsquo;est la vie.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-other-site&#34;&gt;My Other Site&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested you may want to have a look at my travel Blog. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.africanuhambo.co.uk&#34;&gt;African Uhambo&lt;/a&gt;, which describes some overland travel stories about my little family&amp;rsquo;s adventures in contental Europe, over a few years. Since moving to Australia we have not updated it. But will again do so in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>